leicester.gov.uk 2009-10-18

# Internet DisclaimerLeicester City Council -

**IMPORTANT - PLEASE READ**

Information held on this website is intended for your general information and as such should only be treated as a guide. Leicester City Council, “the council”, has used all reasonable endeavours to ensure the accuracy and completeness of this website. It cannot give any representations, assurances, undertakings or warranties about the accuracy, correctness or fitness for purpose regarding the site or any website referred to by it ("third party site").

The council does not approve or endorse any information contained on any third party site and accepts no responsibility for this information or its content. The council therefore accepts no liability in connection with any information held on a third party site. 

The contents of this website are the copyright of the council. You may make copies for your personal use only. You are not allowed to copy and distribute its content in any way without the prior consent of the council. You should seek appropriate professional advice before taking any action based on any information held on this site.

 **Internet Privacy Statement**

This website is run by Leicester City Council. We regard your privacy as important and comply with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

We will only use any personal information you send us for the purposes for which you provide it. We will only hold your information for as long as necessary for these purposes and will not pass it to any other parties unless this is made clear to you. All employees who have access to your personal data or are associated with the handling of that data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal data. 

Upon request to our Data Protection Officer we will inform you whether personal information is stored by us. You may write to: 

Data Protection Officer
Leicester City Council
Welford Place
Leicester
LE1 6ZG

If you have concerns about the processing of your personal data by the council you may contact the Data Protection Officer at the address above, or: 

The Office of the Data Protection Commissioner
Wycliffe House
Water Lane
Wilmslow
Cheshire
SK9 5AF
